

Tommaso Padovan Computer Scientist



5 July 1993



Rhönring 141 Darmstadt, 64289 Germany



+39 3484655214



tommaso.pado@gmail.com

About me ——

Alice is a sensible prepubescent girl from a wealthy English family who finds herself in a strange world ruled by imagination and fantasy. Alice feels comfortable with her identity and has a strong sense that her environment is comprised of clear, logical, and consistent rules and features. Alice's familiarity with the world has led one critic to describe her as a "disembodied intellect". Alice displays great curiosity and attempts to fit her diverse experiences into a clear understanding of the world.

Skills —

Java

polite

outgoing

good manners

pursuer of rabbits

lovely*4 narcissistic*3

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Education

2017

	Specializing in Computer Vision, CUDA and Game Tech stadt" ¹	inology at "TU Darm-
2016	Master degree in Computer Science	Padova (Italy)

Master degree (Erasmus) in Computer Science

Master degree in Computer Science Padova (Italy)
At "Università degli Studi di Padova"²

Darmstadt

2013-2016 Bachelor degree in Computer Science Padova (Italy)

Achieved with 100/110 at "Università degli Studi di Padova"²
2007-2012 High school Treviso (Italy)

Lyceum of Sciences and Informatics

Work Experience

2016-2017 Developer at "Vision Lab Apps srl"³ Part-time Job

Android + back-end of streaming application for smartphones and glasses.

2016 Developer at "Vic World Wide"⁴ Stage

Prototype app for "world 3D reconstruction" using Google-Tango framework

on mobile devices.

2015–2016 Developer at "EasyApp srl"⁵ Freelance Job

Front-end and back-end for ERPs.

[Skills - IT]

php

Programming languages and frameworks

Strong experience with: Discreet experience with:

C++ScalaCUDA C++Python

Java
 Javascript/NodeJS

JuliaHaskellGo

Good knowledge of UML graphical language and UML-editors (e.g. Astah).

¹https://www.informatik.tu-darmstadt.de

²http://www.unipd.it

³http://www.visionlabapps.com

⁴http://vicworldwide.com/it/your-eyes-worldwide

⁵http://www.easyappsrl.it